# **TĂNG THỊ THÙY TRANG**

# **BRAND & COMMUNICATION SPECIALIST**

**©** 0905.58.57.58

(a) tangtrang912003@gmail.com



### **ABOUT ME**

**Short-term goal:** In the next **1 year**, I hope to apply my knowledge and experience to become an excellent Marketing and PR person. I believe that my knowledge and ability to learn will make an important contribution to the development of the Company.

Long-term goal: Become a Brand Manager after 5 years of working in the field of Marketing.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# MARKETING & CONTENT SOCIAL MEDIA | HỌC VIỆN GIÁO HỌC HÀNG KHÔNG VITASA

2024

- Plan and produce content on Facebook, Instagram, and Tiktok channels regularly, reach viewers and **increase followers**, attract new customers.
- Create content, participate in shouting and editing clips Reach 50,000 150,000 views on Tiktok.
- Support content plan & social media management Post regularly and increase **300 followers** in **3 days.**
- · Channel engagement report by week Orientation and production of new content.

## TEACHING ASSISTANT | ANH VĂN HỘI VIỆT MỸ VUS

2023 - 2024

- Support teachers in the teaching process: classroom management (15-20 students/class), distributing materials, preparing learning materials.
- Monitor students' learning, support the evaluation of results (5 weeks) and report periodically to the management department.
- Support students to answer questions, guide revision before class, create conditions for students to master knowledge.

### **SALE ASSISTANT | KUBO & TIMEZONES**

2021 - 2023

- Consult and introduce products/services to customers directly at the store.
- Handle customer inquiries and support answering questions.
- Carry out sales activities: payment, packaging, inventory of goods.
- Support the implementation of planned promotions and discounts.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS - COMMUNICATION**

**2021 - PRESENT** 

Ho Chi Minh City University of Foreign Languages and Information Technology (HUFLIT)

#### **CERTIFICATION**

# MICROSOFT OFFICE SPECIALIST EXCEL 2019 (MOS EXCEL 2019)

### **ACTIVITIES**

# SERIES OF EXHIBITION EVENTS AND TALKSHOW "VAT ÁO TRĂM NĂM"

2024

- Coordinate the event with more than **500 students** attending, coming up with ideas, content, timelines and coordinating guests to attend, receiving positive reviews from guests.
- Prepare MC scripts, technical scripts, thank you letters and thank you emails for speakers.
- Develop skills: time management, event planning, and teamwork.

## WORKSHOP ""LIVE SAVERS - Hành động kịp thời, cứu chữa đúng cách"

2023

- Coordinate to develop program content, design slideshows.
- Assist with speaker presentations and guide students in technical practice sessions.
- **Results:** The program was a success with the participation of **100 students**, receiving positive reviews from the program speakers.

# **TĂNG THỊ THÙY TRANG**

# **BRAND & COMMUNICATION SPECIALIST**

**(a)** 0905.58.57.58

(a) tangtrang912003@gmail.com



# **VỀ TÔI**

**Mục tiêu ngắn hạn:** Trong **1 năm tới**, tôi hy vọng sẽ áp dụng kiến thức và kinh nghiệm của mình để trở thành Marketing và PR xuất sắc. Tôi tin rằng kiến thức và khả năng học hỏi của mình sẽ góp phần quan trọng vào sự phát triển của Công ty.

Mục tiêu dài hạn: Trở thành Brand Manager sau 5 năm làm việc trong lĩnh vực Marketing.

# KINH NGHIỆM LÀM VIỆC

# MARKETING & CONTENT SOCIAL MEDIA | HỌC VIỆN GIÁO HỌC HÀNG KHÔNG VITASA

2024

- Lên kế hoạch và sản xuất nội dung trên các kênh Facebook, Instagram, Tiktok đều đặn, tiếp cận người xem và **tăng lượt theo dõi**, thu hút lượng khách hàng mới.
- Lên nội dung kịch bản, tham gia quay và dựng, chỉnh sửa clip Đạt **50.000 150.000 lượt xem** trên Tiktok
- Hỗ trợ content plan & quản lý social media Lên bài đều đặn và tăng 300 lượt theo dối trong 3 ngày.
- Báo cáo lượng tương tác của các kênh theo tuần Định hướng và sản xuất nội dung mới.

# TRỢ GIẢNG TIẾNG ANH I ANH VĂN HỘI VIỆT MỸ VUS

2023 - 2024

- Hỗ trợ giáo viên trong quá trình giảng dạy: quản lý lớp học (15 20 học viên/lớp), phát tài liệu, chuẩn bị giáo cụ học tập.
- Theo dõi học tập của học viên, hỗ trợ đánh giá kết quả (5 tuần/lần) và báo cáo định kỳcho bộ phận quản lý.
- Hỗ trợ học viên giải đáp thắc mắc, hướng dẫn ôn tập trước giờ học, tạo điều kiện để học viên nắm vững kiến thức.

# NHÂN VIÊN BÁN HÀNG I KUBO & TIMEZONES

2021 - 2023

- Tư vấn và giới thiệu sản phẩm/dịch vụ đến khách hàng trực tiếp tại cửa hàng.
- Xử lý các yêu cầu và hỗ trợ giải đáp thắc mắc của khách hàng.
- Thực hiện các hoạt động bán hàng: thanh toán, đóng gói, kiểm kê hàng hóa.
- Hỗ trợ thực hiện các chương trình khuyến mãi, giảm giá theo kế hoạch.

# **H**OC VẤN

# QUAN HÊ QUỐC TẾ - TRUYỀN THÔNG

2021 - NAY

Đại học Ngoại ngữ - Tin học TP.HCM (HUFLIT)

# **CHỨNG CHỈ**

# MICROSOFT OFFICE SPECIALIST EXCEL 2019 (MOS EXCEL 2019)

## **HOẠT ĐỘNG**

# CHUỗI SỰ KIỆN TRIỂN LÃM VÀ TALKSHOW "VẠT ÁO TRĂM NĂM"

2024

- Phối hợp tổ chức sự kiện với hơn **500 sinh viên** tham dự, lên ý tưởng, nội dung, timeline và điều phối khách mời tham dự, nhân đánh giá tích cực từ khách mời.
- Soan kịch bản MC, kịch bản kỹ thuật, thư cảm ơn và mail cảm ơn cho diễn giả.
- Kỹ năng phát triển: quản lý thời gian, lập kế hoạch sự kiện và làm việc nhóm.

## WORKSHOP ""LIVE SAVERS - Hành động kịp thời, cứu chữa đúng cách"

2023

- Phối hợp xây dựng nội dung chương trình, thiết kế slide trình chiếu.
- Hỗ trợ phần trình bày của diễn giả và hướng dẫn sinh viên trong các phiên thực hành kỹ thuật.
- **Kết quả:** Chương trình thành công với sự tham gia của **100 sinh viên**, nhận đánh giá tích cực từ diễn giả chương trình.